A Guide to the Alberta Arthurs papers FA1507
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Other professional files, 1994-2006; 3; 1.9 Cubic Feet About 4.5 LTR and 1 Half-LTR size Hollinger boxes
  - Pittsburgh Conference/I-DOC - Background to conference and expectations of I-DOC, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 116)
  - The 2006 Dorothy and Lillian Gish Prize, 2005-2006 (Box 10, Folder 117-118)
  - Notes and findings, 1997-2004 (Box 10, Folder 119-120)
    File contains notes, drafts, reports, articles, and publications regarding topics such as funding for the arts, relationships between the nonprofit and for-profit sectors in the arts, cultural diplomacy, and the history of the arts.
  - Venice Biennale, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 121)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 1999-2004 (Box 11, Folder 122-124)
  - Notes from various meetings, 1997-2004 (Box 11, Folder 125-126)
  - Ford Foundation project - Bringing New Media Opportunities to Community-Based Organizations, 2002-2004 (Box 11, Folder 127-128)
  - StreamingCulture projects, 2001-2003 (Box 11, Folder 129)
  - StreamingCulture - Ford Foundation meeting, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 130)
  - Address book, undated (Box 12, Folder 131)